# Kevin Ahmadi

1785 47th Ave. #4 Capitola, CA 95010 **(925) 381-3278** kevinahmadi@gmail.com

## **OBJECTIVE**

To obtain a web development position at a reputable organization working with a team of like-minded, creative, and motivated developers.

### **SUMMARY**

Self-taught web developer with several years of live web experience; background working in psychology and mental health fields. Understands general good practices and web hierarchies. Competent in learning new concepts and data structures. Several years of management experience over large teams in diverse environments.

## **DEVELOPMENT**

**OneWord**, oneword.com

Solo Developer • March 2022 - PRESENT

Community-based word guessing game.

**Squaves**, (Alpha) squaves.com

Solo Developer • July 2021 - PRESENT

Audio uploading and social media website.

**100 Yard Rush**, 100yardrush.com *Solo Developer* • August 2019 - PRESENT

• Random order generator with a game-ified UI.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**7th Avenue Center**, Santa Cruz, CA *Program Director* • SEPT 2015 - PRESENT

- Develop program for a 99-bed inpatient mental health rehabilitation center.
- Manager to a team of 100+ Rehab and Nursing staff. Program Department Manager • SEPT 2013 - SEPT 2015

  Caseload Mental Health Worker • FEB 2012 - SEPT 2013

  Activities Assistant • JUNE 2011 - FEB 2012

  Intern • SEPT 2010 - JUNE 2011

**Web Developer**, Santa Cruz, CA

Freelance • 2008 - PRESENT INTERMITTENT

**Iranian Cinema Channel**, Concord, CA *Assistant General Manager* • 2007 - 2008

### **EDUCATION**

**University of California Santa Cruz**, Santa Cruz, CA Bachelors of Science, Intensive Psychology, 2011

### **PROFICIENCIES**

PHP, OOP and procedural
Javascript (Vanilla & Jquery), AJAX
HTML5 Audio/Video/Canvas
CSS3, CSS Animations
Linux, LAMP, Apache
XML, REST API
MySQL, phpmyadmin, SQLite
GitHub
Video (Adobe Premiere, DaVinci
Resolve)
Audio (Ableton)
Photo (Photoshop, Affinity)

#### **SOFTWARE**

VS Code, Slack, Discord, MAMP Graphics (Photoshop, Affinity) Video (Premiere, DaVinci Resolve) Audio (Ableton, ProTools)

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

Self-taught for 15+ years with a deep understanding of how vanilla PHP, Javascript, HTML, and CSS works without frameworks.

Self-published many projects using LAMP stack.

100 Yard Rush has achieved 100,000+ unique hits during fantasy football season.

Have worked freelance for various small organizations.

### CONNECT

kevinahmadi.com github.com/kevinahmadi twitter.com/kevinahmadi linkedin.com/kevinahmadi